Asian Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Japan., 777 (Box 76–77)
  - Muromachi Period, 1333-1568., 123 (Box 79)
    - Known artists., 95 (Box 80)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 51 (Box 80)
        - Mokuan Reien, -c.1348., 4 (Box 80)
        - Noami, Shinno 1397-1471., 1 (Box 80)
        - Reisai, active 1435., 2 (Box 80)
        - Rinken, Shiba, XVI-XVII C., 1 (Box 80)
        - Ryozen, active mid-XIV C., 2 (Box 80)
        - Sekkyakushi., 1 (Box 80)
        - Sesson, Shukei, 1504-1589., 3 (Box 80)
        - Shikibu., 1 (Box 80)
        - Shiugetsu, XV-XVI C., 1 (Box 80)
        - Shokei, Kenko, active c.1470-1520., 3 (Box 80)
        - Shui, Muto, XIV C., 1 (Box 80)
        - Shuko, 1422-1502., 2 (Box 80)
        - Shutoku, XV C., 1 (Box 80)
        - Soami, -1525., 3 (Box 80)
        - Togan, Unkoku, 1547-1618., 2 (Box 80)
        - Toshun., 1 (Box 80)
        - Yamada Doan, -1571., 1 (Box 80)
        - Yukihide, Kasuga, XV C., 1 (Box 80)
      - Individual artists, A-Z., 44 (Box 80)
        - Josetsu, active early XV C., 5 (Box 80)
        - Mitsunobu, Tosa, 1434-1525., 8 (Box 80)
        - Motonobu, Kano, 1476-1559., 6 (Box 80)
        - Sesshu Toyo, 1420-1506., 12 (Box 80)
        - Shubun, Tensho, active c.1400-1450., 13 (Box 80)
  - Momoyama Period., 169 (Box 80)
    - Unknown artists., 58 (Box 81)
      - Miscellaneous works., 51 (Box 81)
      - Namban Byobu (Westerners in Japan)., 7 (Box 81)
    - Known artists., 111 (Box 81)
      - Miscellaneous artists., 31 (Box 81)
        - Chokuan, Soga, -1610., 1 (Box 81)
        - Hideyori, Kano, -1557., 1 (Box 81)
        - Koetsu, Honami, 1558-1637., 1 (Box 81)
        - Kyuzo, Hasegawa, 1568-1593., 1 (Box 81)
        - Motonobu, Kano., 1 (Box 81)
        - Naganobu, Kano, 1577-1654., 2 (Box 81)
        - Roshu, Fukai, 1699-1755., 2 (Box 81)
        - Sansetsu, Kano, 1589-1651., 2 (Box 81)
        - Shoei, Kano, 1519-1592., 1 (Box 81)
        - Shojo, Nakamura, 1589-1639., 4 (Box 81)
          Name also given as Shokado Shojo.
        - Soshu, Kano, 1551-1601., 1 (Box 81)
        - Sotatsu, School of., 2 (Box 81)
        - Takanobu, Kano, 1571-1618., 1 (Box 81)
        - Togan, Unkoku, 1547-1618., 3 (Box 81)
        - Yoshinobu, Kano, 1552-1640., 4 (Box 81)
        - Yusetsu, Kaihoku, 1598-1677., 2 (Box 81)
        - Yusho, Kaiho, 1533-1615., 2 (Box 81)
      - Individual artists, A-Z., 80 (Box 81)
        - Eitoku, Kano, 1543-1590., 12 (Box 81)
        - Mitsunobu, Kano, 1565-1608., 4 (Box 81)
        - Naizen, Kano, 1570-1616., 9 (Box 82)
        - Sanraku, Kano, 1559-1635., 12 (Box 82)
        - Sotatsu, Tawayara, 1576-1643., 34 (Box 82)
        - Tohaku, Hasegawa, 1539-1610., 9 (Box 82)
  - Edo Period, 1600-1868., 293 (Box 82)
    - Unknown artists., 53 (Box 82)
    - Known artists., 240 (Box 82)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 159 (Box 82)
        - Ando, Kaigetsudo, active early XVIII C., 1 (Box 83)
        - Baiho, Shinruisai, active c.1800., 2 (Box 83)
        - Basho, Matsuo, 1644-1694., 1 (Box 83)
        - Beisanjin, Okada, 1744-1818., 1 (Box 83)
        - Bosai, Kameda, 1752-1826., 1 (Box 83)
        - Buncho, Tani, 1764-1840., 1 (Box 83)
        - Bunkaku., 1 (Box 83)
        - Bunrei, Kato, 1706-1782., 1 (Box 83)
        - Bunrin, Shiokawa, 1808-1877., 1 (Box 83)
        - Chikuden, Tanomura, 1777-1835., 2 (Box 83)
        - Chikudo, Kishi, 1826-1897., 1 (Box 83)
        - Chikuto, Nakabayashi, 1776-1853., 2 (Box 83)
        - Chinzan, Tsubaki, 1801-1854., 1 (Box 83)
        - Choshun, Miyagawa, 1682-1752., 1 (Box 83)
        - Eishi, Hosoda, 1756-1829., 1 (Box 83)
        - Ganku, Saeki, 1749-1838., 3 (Box 83)
        - Ganryo, Kishi, 1798-1852., 1 (Box 83)
        - Gantai, Kishi, 1784-1865., 1 (Box 83)
        - Genki, Komai, 1747-1797., 1 (Box 83)
        - Genkyu, Yamamoto, active late XVII C., 1 (Box 83)
        - Goshun, Matsumura, XIX C., 2 (Box 83)
        - Gukei, Sumiyoshi, 1631-1705., 2 (Box 83)
        - Gyokusen, Mochizuki, 1794-1852., 2 (Box 83)
        - Hanko, Okada, 1782-1846., 2 (Box 83)
        - Harunobu, Suzuki, 1724-1770., 1 (Box 83)
        - Hiromori, Sumiyoshi, 1705-1777., 2 (Box 83)
        - Hoen, Nishiyama, 1804-1867., 1 (Box 83)
        - Hoitsu, Sakai, 1761-1828., 4 (Box 83)
        - Hokuba, Arisaka, 1771-1844., 2 (Box 83)
        - Hyakusen, Sakaki, 1698-1753., 2 (Box 83)
        - Ippo, Mori, 1798-1871., 1 (Box 83)
        - Isen'in, Kano, 1775-1828., 1 (Box 83)
        - Jakuchu, Ito, 1716-1800., 4 (Box 83)
        - Kawabata Gyokushu, 1842-1913., 1 (Box 83)
        - Kazan, Watanabe, 1793-1841., 3 (Box 83)
        - Keibun, Matsumura, 1779-1843., 4 (Box 83)
        - Kenkado, Kimura, 1736-1802., 1 (Box 83)
        - Kenzan, Ogata, 1663-1743., 1 (Box 83)
        - Ki, Komai, 1747-1797., 1 (Box 83)
        - Kien, Yanagisawa, 1706-1758., 1 (Box 83)
        - Koi, Kano, c.1569-1636., 2 (Box 83)
        - Kokan, Shiba, 1747-1818., 2 (Box 83)
        - Koryusai, Isoda, active 1764-1788., 3 (Box 83)
        - Koyetsu., 1 (Box 83)
        - Kuniteru., 1 (Box 83)
        - Kuniyoshi, Igusa, 1797-1861., 1 (Box 83)
        - Kyosho, Tachihara, 1785-1840., 1 (Box 83)
        - Matabe, Iwasa, 1578-1650., 2 (Box 83)
        - Mitsuoki, Tosa, 1617-1691., 1 (Box 83)
        - Mitsusada, Tosa, -1806., 1 (Box 83)
        - Morikage, Kusumi, c.1620-1690., 2 (Box 83)
        - Moronobu, Hishigawa, 1625-1694., 1 (Box 83)
        - Naganobu, Kano, 1577-1654., 1 (Box 83)
        - Nangaku, Watanabe, 1767-1813., 2 (Box 83)
        - Nankai, Gion, 1677-1751., 1 (Box 83)
        - Naonobu, Kano, 1607-1650., 3 (Box 83)
        - Oho, Sakai, 1808-1841., 1 (Box 83)
        - Renzan, Aoki, 1805-1859., 1 (Box 83)
        - Ritsuo, Ogawa Kan, 1663-1747., 4 (Box 83)
        - Rosetsu, Nagasawa, 1755-1799., 4 (Box 83)
        - Roshu, Fukae, 1699-1757., 1 (Box 83)
        - Sansetsu, Kano, 1589-1651., 2 (Box 84)
        - San-Yo, Rai, 1780-1832., 1 (Box 84)
        - Seiki, Yokoyama, 1792-1864., 1 (Box 84)
        - Seisen, Kano, 1796-1846., 2 (Box 84)
        - Sekkei, Yamaguchi, 1644-1732., 1 (Box 84)
        - Sengai, Gibon, 1750-1837., 2 (Box 84)
        - Settei, Tsukioka, 1710-1786., 1 (Box 84)
        - Shigenobu, Kamo, c.1625-1650., 1 (Box 84)
        - Shiko, Watanabe, 1683-1755., 2 (Box 84)
        - Shohaku, Soga, -1781., 3 (Box 84)
        - Shunko, Katsukawa, -1827., 1 (Box 84)
        - Shunman, Kubo, 1757-1820., 1 (Box 84)
        - Sohei, Takahashi, 1804-1834., 1 (Box 84)
        - Somin, Yokoya, 1669-1733., 1 (Box 84)
        - Sorai, Ogyu, 1668-1728., 1 (Box 84)
        - Sosen, Mori, 1747-1821., 3 (Box 84)
        - Sohei, Takahashi, 1804-1834., 1 (Box 84)
        - Sori, Tawaraya, active c.1764-1780., 1 (Box 84)
        - Sotatsu, Tawaraya, 1576-1643., 1 (Box 84)
        - Sukenobu, Nishikawa, 1671-1751., 2 (Box 84)
        - Tanyu, Kano, 1602-1674., 2 (Box 84)
        - Tocho, Hasegawa, active 1624-1643., 1 (Box 84)
        - Tosa Mitsunori, 1583-1638., 1 (Box 84)
        - Toshu, Tamate, 1795-1871., 1 (Box 84)
        - Toyoharu, Utagawa, 1735-1814., 1 (Box 84)
        - Toyohiko, Okamoto, 1773-1845., 2 (Box 84)
        - Toyohiro, Utagawa, 1773-1828., 2 (Box 84)
        - Toyokuni, Utagawa, 1769-1825., 2 (Box 84)
        - Tsunemasa, Kawamata, active 1716-1748., 1 (Box 84)
        - Utamaro, Kitagawa, 1754-1806., 1 (Box 84)
        - Yasunobu, Kano, 1613-1685., 2 (Box 84)
        - Yosai, Kikuchi, 1788-1878., 1 (Box 84)
        - Yukinobu, Kiyohara, 1643-1682., 2 (Box 84)
        - Yusen, Kano, 1778-1815., 1 (Box 84)
        - Zaichu, Hara, 1750-1837., 1 (Box 84)
        - Zensetsu, Tokuriki., 1 (Box 84)
        - Zeshin, Shibata, 1807-1891., 1 (Box 84)
      - Individual artists, A-Z., 81 (Box 84)
        - Buson, Yosa, 1716-1783., 8 (Box 84)
        - Gyokudo, Uragami, 1754-1820., 7 (Box 84)
        - Hiroshige, Ando, 1797-1858., 6 (Box 84)
        - Hokusai, Katsushika, 1760-1849., 6 (Box 84)
        - Ikkei, Ukita, 1763-1837., 5 (Box 84)
        - Korin, Ogata, 1663-1743., 17 (Box 85)
        - Mokubei, Aoki, 1767-1833., 5 (Box 85)
        - Okyo, Maruyama, 1733-1795., 5 (Box 85)
        - Sumiyoshi, School of., 9 (Box 85)
        - Taiga, Ikeno, 1723-1776., 8 (Box 85)
        - Tanyu, Kano, 1602-1674., 5 (Box 85)
  - Meiji Period (Modern)., 10 (Box 85)
    Includes two folders of miscellaneous clippings.
    - Known artists., 10 (Box 85)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 10 (Box 85)
        - Deguchi, Onisaburo, 1871-1948., 2 (Box 85)
        - Hori, Tetsuzan., 1 (Box 85)
        - Kaivase, Hasui, 2 (Box 85)
        - Kawabata, Ryushi, 1885-1966., 1 (Box 85)
        - Kikuchi, Keigetsu., 1 (Box 85)
        - Takamura, Masawo., 1 (Box 85)
        - Urushibara, Yoshijiro., 1 (Box 85)
        - Yoshida, Hiroshi., 1 (Box 85)